A Guide to the San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Records, 1931-2008 (bulk 1985-2005)
San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Records
- Programs
  - The San Antonio Community Education Leadership Program Application Booklet,2001 (Box 50)
  - Diversity Awareness Program,October 21, 1995 (Box 50)
  - The City of San Antonio Presents the Municipal Leadership Institute,March 15, 1997 (Box 50)
  - 1999 Hispanic Chamber Leadership Program,1999-2000 (Box 50)
  - (Box 50)
- Events and Awards
  This series documents the social and formal events sponsored by the SAHCC. Among these events are awards ceremonies and recognition luncheons for local businesses, business owners, and supporters of local businesses; golf tournaments; events with speakers; installation banquets for the Board of Directors; and networking mixers for members. There is also information about seminars, conferences, and programs sponsored or co-sponsored by the Chamber.
  - Event Planning (Box 1)
    - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Target 2100: San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 3-year Strategic Plan, 1997-2000 (Box 47)
    - Diecis?is de Septiembre "Noche Mexicana",1999 (Box 47)
    - "Noche Mexicana" Correspondence with Marriott,2000 (Box 47)
    - Alexander E. Brise?o Luncheon,2001 (Box 47)
    - Hispanic Chamber Board Meeting and Alexander E. Brise?o Leadership Development Program Luncheon, 2001 (Box 47)
    - 2001 Business Networking Mixer,2001 (Box 47)
    - Hispanic Chamber and SiTV's (Latino Laugh) Business Networking Mixer, 2001 (Box 47)
    - 2001 Fiesta S.A. Commission,2000-2001 (Box 47)
    - 2001 Making Sense of the Numbers, Census Breakfast, 2001 (Box 47)
    - 2001 Mayoral Debate, 2001 (Box 47)
    - Minority Enterprise Development Week Golf Tournament, 1999 and 2001 (Box 47)
    - Minority Enterprise Development Week Golf Tournament, 2001 (Box 47)
    - Minority Enterprise Development Week and Golf Tournament, 2001 (Box 47)
    - 6th Annual Diecis? de Septiembre "Noche Mexicana Celebration", 1999-2003 (Box 47)
    - 6th Annual Diecis? de Septiembre "Noche Mexicana Celebration", 2001 (Box 48)
    - National Society of Hispanic MBA's 2001 National Convention Kickoff Reception, 2001 (Box 48)
    - Public Relations Committee for the San Antonio Local Organizing Committee 2002 Women's Final Four, 2001 (Box 48)
    - 2001 River Parade Pachanga, 2001 (Box 48)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Correspondence with La Mansion del Rio Hotel, 2001 (Box 48)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 8th Annual Golf Tournament, 2001 (Box 48)
    - 2002 Strategic Planning Session at La Mansion, 2001 (Box 48)
    - U.S.-Mexico Economic Outlook Conference and "Noche Mexicana" Celebration, 2001 (Box 48)
    - Bioscience Conference, 2002 (Box 48)
    - Bioscience Conference Committee, 2002 (Box 48)
    - Bioscience Conference Special Events, 2002 (Box 48)
    - "Noche Mexicana" Celebration, 2002 (Box 48)
    - 2001 Business Networking Mixer: San Antonio Spurs, 2001 (Box 49)
    - 2001 Business Networking Mixer: Sunset Station, 2001 (Box 49)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce and The Greater San Antonio Chamber of Commerce Joint Business Networking Mixer, 2001 (Box 49)
    - Lunch with Santa, 2001 (Box 49)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce and Laredo National Bank: San Antonio Business Networking Mixer, 2001 (Box 49)
    - Hispanic Chamber Partnership Mixer: Fiesta at the Plaza, 2001 (Box 49)
    - 2001 Minority Enterprise Development Week Golf Tournament, 2001 (Box 49)
    - Event Flyers, Sign-up Sheets, and Related Documents, 2001-2002 (Box 49)
  - Events (Box 12)
    - 2001 Events (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Annual Banquet, 1985, 1987, 1994, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Business Success Series Recognition Luncheon, 1989-1996 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Celebrate Latino Art 2005: "Imagenes de Mi Pueblo" poster, April 12, 2005 (Drawer 70)
    - Chiapas Delegration Breakfast, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Cinco de Mayo Celebration, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Club Raices Meeting, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Consul Events, 1990-1997 and undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Diez y Seis Celebration, 1992-1993 and undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Dieciseis de Septiembre, 1994-1999 and undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Emerging Business Awards, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Emerging Issues Forum, September 20, 2011 (Box 47)
    - Events for Honorees, 1988-2003 and undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Events with Speakers, 1989-2001 and undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Golf Tournaments, 1994-2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Grand Opening Block Party for Casa de Mexico International Building, undated (Box 47)
    - Hispanic Chamber Leadership Program: Class of 2000 Graduation Ceremony,April 13, 2000 (Box 47)
    - Installation Banquet, 1986-2005 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Invitations to SAHCC, 1991, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Mixers, 1989-1997 and undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Noche de Amistad, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Noche de Loter? Los Dons y Dode Negocio with Loter?Set, July 31, 2006 (Box 49)
      - Noche de Loter? Los Dons y Dode Negocio poster, July 31, 2006 (Drawer 69)
    - Noche Mexicana Gala, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - SAHCC 75th Anniversary, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Seminars, Conferences, and Programs, 1985-2002and undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Frank Tejeda Event, August 23, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Texas High School Project Reception and DinnerMarch 10, 2005 (Box 47)
    - United States-Mexico Economic Outlook Conference,September 14, 2001 (Box 47)
    - United States-Mexico Economic Outlook Conference,September 14, 2001 (Box 49)
    - Welcome Receptions, 1996, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Women's Equality Day, August 27, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Other SAHCC Events, 1987-2000and undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Awards (Box 13)
    - Awards, 1964, 1988, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Business and Achievement Awards, 1995-2004 (Box 49)
    - Business Awards, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Emerging Business Awards, 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Leadership Awards, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Small Business Awards, 1989-1997and undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Events, Invitations, Flyers, and Programs1994-2006 (Box 49)
- Publicity
  This series includes newsclippings, press releases from the Chamber office, and scrapbooks which recount the activities and work of the Mexican Chamber between 1948 and 2001. The clippings are from as early as 1950, but the bulk of the newsclippings run from 1987 to 2000. The newsclippings chronicle the activities of the Chamber from its early years as the Mexican Chamber of Commerce through its many changes, including the 1987 name change. The articles cover Chamber events and banquets, member affiliations with local businesses, and SAHCC support of local woman- and minority-owned businesses. Articles were also collected if a Chamber member was mentioned in them, or if the articles would be of interest to the Chamber and its Mexican-American audience. Included are a number of articles about the Chamber's role and support of the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA).
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 43)
  - Magazine Coverage, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - News clippings (Box 9)
    - Newsclippings, 1950, 1964-1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings, February 1988 – December 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings, January 1989 – December 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Newsclippings, January 1990 – November 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, January 1991 – July 1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings, August 1991 – December 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Newsclippings, February – December 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings, January – April, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings, May – December, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Newsclippings 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, January – September 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings, 2000-2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Newsclippings from the San Antonio Express News Online Archive (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - “People You Should Know” Promotion (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Request for San Antonio Express News Community Service Ads (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - San Antonio Mission Articles with Las Misiones invitation,August-September 2003 (Box 50)
  - SAHCC logo, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbooks (Oversize Materials) (Box 37)
    - 1952–1955, 1960, 1961 (Box 37)
    - 1945, 1948, 1949–1953, 1950–1951, 1951–1952 (Box 38)
    - 1964, 1964–1965, 1966–1968 (Box 39)
  - Think Big Buy Small Advertising Campaign, 2002and undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Photographic Materials
  These photographs provide information about Chamber members (including Board members), events, and activities within the San Antonio community. Important, older photographs include the Mexican Chamber of Commerce (1931) and a group photograph of attendees of the First Mexican Chamber of Commerce Convention (1939). Also of note is a group of oversize portraits of Board Chairs, spanning the years 1931 to 1999.
  Other photographs include images of events the Chamber and its members have participated in over the years; Chamber members with presidents of the United States of America and visiting foreign presidents; group photographs of Chamber members participating in events and ceremonies (including banquets, receptions and ribbon-cuttings for new businesses) (1995-2002); a series of Mexican and Mexican-American celebrities; and scrapbooks (1980-1995) in which some people and events are identified.
  - Dated by Year (Box 13)
    - First San Antonio Mexican Chamber of Commerce, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Mexican Chamber Members, 1954, 1960, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Photographs, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - People (Box 13)
    - Award Winners and Member Companies, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors (Box 13)
      - 1996 (color photographs) (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - 1996 (black and white photographs) (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - 1997 (color photographs) (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - 1997 (black and white photographs) (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - 2001 (color photographs) (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - 2001 (black and white photographs) (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Undated (color photographs) (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Undated (black and white photographs) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bennie J. Cantu, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Henry Cisneros (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Fortunado De Los Santos, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Carlos Freymann with Visiting Foreign Presidents, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Henry B. Gonzales and Ann Richards, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Ramon Galindo, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Henry B. Gonzales, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Chas Kuper, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Richard Limon, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Ray Padilla, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Marty Rodriguez, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Dr. Candelario Saenz, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Weiss and P.J. Morales Jr., undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - AJ Rodriguez, Dan Markson, Ruth McClendon, and Frank Tejeda, undated (Box 49)
    - Identified Portraits A-J, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Identified Portraits, K-Z, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Past Presidents (Box 40)
      - 1931-1959 (Box 40)
      - 1960-1983 (Box 41)
      - 1986-1990 (Box 42)
      - Manuel Leal (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Identified Groups of People, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Proofs, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Staff, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Women, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified groups of people, undated. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Portraits, undated. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified Portraits – Black and White, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Events (Box 15)
    - 1st Retreat, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 75th Anniversary Photographs (Box 49)
    - Access to Capital Luncheon, May 22, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Actors, Talent Events, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Aguas Calientes, June 1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Aida Alvarez Reception, January 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Alameda, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Alamo Frame, September 1998 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Alex Brise?o Christmas Pictures, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - America Can Compete Event, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Amigos Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Annual Achievements Awards, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Annual Banquet, January 1997 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Assist – Trinity University, October 2, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - ATandT Legislative Reception, December 1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Attorney General's Luncheon, August 13, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Awards Banquet, October 15, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Awards Ceremony, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Avenida Guadalupe Association Mixer, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Bank of America 25k Donation, January 9, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Banquet, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
    - Breakfast, May 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Breakfast with Council, January 2, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Breakfast with the Consul October, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Breakfast with the Consul, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Breakfast with Consul Jennifer Pe?a-Swairline, Feb/March, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Breakfast with Consul, July 1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Beer Industry Events, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Booksigning – Lionel Sosa, May 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Boxers, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Boy Scouts Events, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Brisino LDP, May 17, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Broadway Bank Groundbreaking, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - BSS – Alfred Flores, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Business Achievement Award Luncheon, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Business Development Break, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Business Development Breakfast – The American Dream, May 1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Business Development Breakfast – The Year 2000 Computer Crisis, March 1998 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Business Meet and Greet, September 25, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Business Networking Mixers, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Business Success Meeting, February 1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Business Success Series Luncheon, November 1997 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Candid, April 2002 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Candid Photos, October 19, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Carusi Rims Ribbon Cutting, undated. (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Celebration with Art Flores, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - CEO, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Christmas Celebration, December 2001 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Christmas Celebration, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Christmas in July, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - A Christmas Wish Event, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Cinco de Mayo, May 3, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Cinco de Mayo, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Cinco de Mayo Celebrations, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Conference – NABC, February 15-19, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Consul's Annual Event, December 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Consuls Breakfast, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Consul's Luncheon, November (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Corporate Partner Reception, December 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - CPS, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Creative Civilization/Garcia LKS, October-November 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Delores Mu?os Luncheon, December 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Dieciseis Event, September 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Dieciseis de Septiembre Gala, Noche Mexicana, September 1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Dragon VIP, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Economic Outlook Conference, January 1, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Eddie Goodbye Lunch, July 1998 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Embajodoes Appreciation Reception, December 4, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Emergency Issues Forum, December 2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Fall Membership Campaign, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Falstaff Family Christmas Party, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Farewell to Leo, May 21, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Fiesta Kickoff, April 19, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Fiesta Kickoff, April 19, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - First Mexican Chamber of Commerce Convention, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Ford Salute to Education, November 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Formal Event with Rick Perry and Henry Cisneros, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Free Trade Picture, November 7, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Frost Bank, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Get Out and Vote – Business Day at the Polls, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Golf, March 16, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Golf, June 12, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Golftown, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Golf Tournament, October 9, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Golf Tournament, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Gourmet Texas Ribbon Cutting, October 1996 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Government Day LSA XXIX, undated. (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Governor's Conference, Texans for Tourists, December 1961 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony, [1940s] (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Groundbreaking with Diamond Shamrock, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Guadalajara, Mexico Trip, August 1976 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Hair Salon Ribbon Cutting, undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Hard Rock Caf? Latino, June 7, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Hector Barreto U.S. Small Business representative, May 9, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - HemisFair Construction, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Hispanic Association of Colleges and Universities Conference, Early 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Hispanic Business Profiles, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - The Hispanic Chamber, December 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic Chamber Leadership Program/Breakfast with Council, October 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Hispanic Chamber Leadership Reception, March 1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Hispanic Leadership Project, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Hispanic Professional Leadership Conference, November 1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Food Baskets, undated. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Hope Andrade Installation, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Installation Banquet, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Installation Banquet – 69th, January 1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Installation Banquet – 70th Annual, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Installation Banquet – 71st Annual, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Installation Banquet, January 2001 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Installation Banquet – 72nd Annual, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Installation Banquet, January 16, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
    - Installation Banquet, 73rd Annual, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Installation Banquet/Meet the Buyer, January 2002 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Installation Dinner/Dance, 1959and undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - John Gary Goodbye, December 1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - “Juntos Somos Mas” Camp, March/April 1996 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - John F. Kennedy, “Alliance for Progress” Distinguished Service Award to William Gilbert Short, 5-25-1962 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - KVDA Mixer, May 25 – undated. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Las Ferias de Septembre Press Conference, August 1996 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - La Kantabria Ribbion Cutting, June 1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Latino Laff, May 8, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Legislative Reception, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Leadership Business and Professionals, March 6, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Leadership Class, March 16, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Leadership Class, March 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Convention, August – September 2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Golf Tournament, June 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Leadership San Antonio, January 4, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Leadership San Antonio, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Light the Fire Within, December 11, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - LSA Golf Tournament – 6th Annual, June 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - LSA Golf Tournament, June 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - LSA (Leadership San Antonio), November 5, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - LSA Quality of Life Day, January 7, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - LSA Reception Class 29, September 22, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - LSA Tournament – 4th Annual, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Luncheon – Governor o Tamaulpias, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - March Madness Event, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Mayoral Debate, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mayoral/Council Reception, June 24, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Mays Family – Bank of America Donation, June 25, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - MBA Graduation, June 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Meeting of the Business Services Mall Task Force, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Meet the Buyer, January 2002 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Meet the Buyer, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Meet the Buyer and Leadership Protocol, March 1996 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Meet the Buyer – Gem Sector, October 1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Meet the Buyer Seminar – Piatte's Restaurant, May 16, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Membership Campaign Awards, 1959and undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Membership Campaign, October 1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Membership Campaign Drive, August 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Membership Kickoff Lunch, undated. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Meritorious Service Awards, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Merry Maid's Ribbon Cutting, October 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Mexican Revolution Ceremony, December 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Minority Business Development Foundation, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Awards Ceremonies, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Ribbon Cutting, October 1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Mission Trails Press Conference, February 1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Mixers, 1991, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Mixer, April 16, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Mixer – Chamber Partnership – Business, October 1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Mixer – Fiesta, April 1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Mixer – Fiesta Del Grito, September 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Mixer – Rhythm of the Night, August 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Mixer – San Antonio Museum of Art, May 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Monte Carlo Casino Night, August 22, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - New Member Meeting, February 1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - New Member Orientation, July 1998 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - New Member Orientation, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Newsletter Pictures, January – February 2002 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Newsletter Pictures, March – April 2002 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Newsletter Pictures, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Office Construction, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Opening of Centeno Theaters, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Pablo's Grove, Members Gathering, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Pablo's Grove, Members Gathering, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Parade Events, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Past Chairman Reception, August 21, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Pepsi Procurement, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Police Chief Albert Ortiz – Luncheon, May 20, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 33)